Guide to the Carl Van Vechten Papers Relating to African American Arts and Letters
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1932–1964; Series IV; 157.31 linear feet
  - Unselected Photographic Prints, 13.14 linear feet
    - Portraits
      - Peterson, Jerome Sidney, 1937 July 11; 5 photographic prints (Box 135, Folder 2532)
      - Peterson, Louis, 1960 August 9; 4 photographic prints (Box 135, Folder 2533)
      - Petry, Ann, 1948 November 12; 19 photographic prints (Box 135, Folder 2534)
      - Pippin, Horace, at the home of Albert C. (Albert Coombs) Barnes, Lower Merion Township, Pennsylvania, 1940 February 4; 4 photographic prints (Box 135, Folder 2535)
      - Pittman, Evelyn La Rue, 1962 September 18; 2 photographic prints (Box 135, Folder 2536)
      - Polk, Oscar, 1937 January 24; 9 photographic prints (Box 135, Folder 2537)
      - Price, Leontyne, 1951 December 11; 11 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2538)
        Inscriptions on versos of some prints misidentify the roll number.
      - Price, Leontyne, as Bess in Porgy and Bess, musical composed by George Gershwin, libretto by DuBose Heyward and Ira Gershwin, 1953 May 19; 40 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2539-2540)
      - Primus, Pearl, 1943 October 11; 26 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2541)
      - Primus, Pearl, in Hard Time Blues, dance choreographed by Pearl Primus, 1943 October 11; 18 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2542)
      - Rahn, Muriel, as Carmen Jones in Carmen Jones, musical with music by Georges Bizet and book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, 1944 February 29; 37 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2543)
      - Rahn, Muriel, as Carmen Jones in Carmen Jones, musical with music by Georges Bizet and book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, 1944 February 29; 47 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2544-2545)
      - Rahn, Muriel, as Cora Lewis in The Barrier, musical with music by Jan Meyerowitz and book and lyrics by Langston Hughes, 1950 January 29; 13 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2546)
      - Ramsay, Edith, 1932 March 21; 1 photographic print (Box 136, Folder 2547)
      - Ramsay, Edith, 1934 August 20; 1 photographic print (Box 136, Folder 2548)
      - Ramsay, Edith, 1935 December 24; 2 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2549)
      - Reading, Bertice, 1959 January 6; 2 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2550)
      - Reading, Bertice, 1959 January 6; 7 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2551)
      - Richer, Clément, at Paris, France, 1949 October 9; 6 photographic prints (Box 136, Folder 2552)
      - Robeson, Eslanda Goode, 1933 June 1; 2 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2553)
      - Robeson, Eslanda Goode, 1936 January 10; 1 photographic print (Box 137, Folder 2554)
      - Robeson, Eslanda Goode, and Paul Robeson, 1933 June 1; 8 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2555)
      - Robeson, Paul, 1932 March 7; 41 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2556-2557)
      - Robeson, Paul, 1933 June 1; 19 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2558)
      - Robeson, Paul, 1936 January 10; 17 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2559)
      - Robeson, Paul, as Othello in Othello, play by William Shakespeare, 1944 June 1; 17 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2560)
      - Robeson, Paul, as Othello in Othello, play by William Shakespeare, 1944 June 1; 9 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2561)
      - Robeson, Paul, as Othello in Othello, play by William Shakespeare, 1944 June 1; 33 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2562-2563)
      - Robeson, Paul, Jr., 1942 July 8; 4 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2564)
      - Robin, Wilson, 1942 September 30; 2 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2565)
      - Robinson, Bill, 1933 January 25; 12 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2566)
      - Robinson, Bill, 1933 January 25; 3 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2567)
      - Robinson, Bill, 1941 April 18; 26 photographic prints (Box 137, Folder 2568)
      - Robinson, Bill, 1941 April 18; 33 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2569)
      - Robinson, Bill, 1941 April 18; 46 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2570-2571)
      - Robinson, Bill, at Harlem, New York City, 1932 February 6; 4 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2572)
      - Robinson-Wayne, Beatrice, as St. Theresa I in Four Saints in Three Acts, musical by Virgil Thomson with a libretto by Gertrude Stein, 1934 March 9; 1 photographic print (Box 138, Folder 2573)
      - Rodgers, Guy, 1958 May 24; 9 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2574)
        Rodgers wears his basketball uniform for Temple University. In a images he holds a basketball that commemorates his school career record of 1,545 points
      - Rodgers, Guy, and Elaine Vance, 1958 May 24; 6 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2575)
      - Rodriguez, Percy, 1960 June 7; 1 photographic print (Box 138, Folder 2576)
      - Sampson, Edith S. (Edith Spurlock), 1949 April 6; 9 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2577)
      - Sands, Diana, 1963 January 29; 9 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2578)
      - Sands, Diana, as Adelaide Smith in Tiger, Tiger Burning Bright, play by Peter S. Feibleman, 1963 January 29; 66 photographic prints Housed in 3 folders (Box 138, Folder 2579-2581)
      - Savage, Archie, 1942 March 2; 19 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2582)
      - Savage, Archie, 1942 March 2; 2 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2583)
      - Savage, Augusta, 1938 July 9; 3 photographic prints (Box 138, Folder 2584)
      - Schuyler, George S. (George Samuel), 1941 July 2; 17 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2585)
      - Schuyler, Josephine, 1948 February 18; 4 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2586)
      - Schuyler, Josephine, and Philippa Schuyler, 1946 July 22; 2 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2587)
      - Schuyler, Philippa, 1946 May 31; 16 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2588)
      - Schuyler, Philippa, 1946 July 22; 11 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2589)
      - Schuyler, Philippa, 1949 February 22; 4 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2590)
      - Schuyler, Philippa, 1949 February 22; 6 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2591)
      - Schuyler, Philippa, 1951 May 9; 3 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2592)
      - Schuyler, Philippa, 1951 May 9; 3 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2593)
      - Schuyler, Philippa, at Fisk University, Nashville, Tennessee, 1947 April 26; 1 photographic print (Box 139, Folder 2594)
      - Scott, Harold, 1959 February 17; 3 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2595)
      - Scott, Henry Benjamin, 1945 Janaury 19; 4 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2596)
      - Shirley, George, 1961 October 10; 12 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2597)
        Includes prints with erroneous roll inscriptions
      - Short, Bobby, 1962 January 3; 3 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2598)
      - Sissle, Noble, 1951 November 20; 6 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2599)
      - Smith, Bessie, 1936 February 3; 59 photographic prints Housed in 3 folders (Box 139, Folder 2600-2602)
      - Smith, Muriel as Carmen Jones in Carmen Jones, musical with music by Georges Bizet and book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, 1944 December 18; 14 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2603)
      - Smith, Muriel as Carmen Jones in Carmen Jones, musical with music by Georges Bizet and book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, 1944 December 18; 8 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2604)
      - Smith, William Gardner, 1948 December 10; 14 photographic prints (Box 139, Folder 2605)
      - Spearman, Rawn W. (Rawn Wardell), 1952 January 12; 4 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2606)
      - Still, William Grant, 1949 March 12; 9 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2607)
      - Stinnett, McCleary, 1933 April 22; 2 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2608)
      - Stokes, Al, 1934 March 30; 7 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2609)
      - Stokes, Al, as Heywood Parsons in They Shall Not Die, play by John Wexley, 1934 March 30; 1 photographic print (Box 140, Folder 2610)
      - Strayhorn, Billy, 1958 August 19; 7 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2611)
      - Sullivan, Maxine, 1941 October 7; 42 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2612-2613)
      - Swanson, Howard, 1951 April 4; 5 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2614)
      - Tann, Wesley, 1962 May 1; 5 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2615)
      - Taylor, Dorothy, 1964 June 24; 6 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2616)
      - Thayer, Alonzo, 1932 June 18; 2 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2617)
      - Thayer, Alonzo, 1935 November 25; 1 photographic print (Box 140, Folder 2618)
      - Thayer, Alonzo, 1935 November 25; 5 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2619)
      - Thomas, Edna, 1932 June 18; 3 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2620)
      - Thomas, Edna, 1948 March 8; 4 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2621)
      - Thomas, Edna, as Mexican Woman in A Streetcar Named Desire, play by Tennessee Williams, 1948 March 8; 12 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2622)
      - Thomas, Lloyd, 1938 December 8; 3 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2623)
      - Thompson, Claude, as Islander in Jamaica, musical with music by Harold Arlen and book by E.Y. Harburg and Fred Saidy, 1959 February 5; 5 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2624)
      - Tuguese as Chief Burah in Kykunkor (The Witch Woman), opera by Asadata Dafora, 1935 January 14; 12 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2625)
      - Tyler, Veronica, 1961 April 11; 2 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2626)
      - Tynes, Margaret, 1959 September 14; 1 photographic print (Box 140, Folder 2627)
      - Tynes, Margaret, 1959 September 23; 18 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2628)
      - Tynes, Margaret, 1959 September 23; 19 photographic prints (Box 140, Folder 2629)
      - Tynes, Margaret, as Carmen in Carmen, opera by Georges Bizet and libretto by Henri Meilhac and Ludovic Halévy, 1959 September 23; 1 photographic print (Box 140, Folder 2630)
      - Valentine, Grace, 1932 April 13; 1 photographic print (Box 140, Folder 2631)
      - Van Dyke, Henry, 1961 September 26; 8 photographic prints (Box 141, Folder 2632)
      - Van Dyke, Henry, 1962 November 13; 69 photographic prints. Housed in 3 folders. (Box 141, Folder 2633-2635)
      - Van Vechten, Carl, and Richard Wright, 1946 March 8; 1 photographic print (Box 141, Folder 2636)
      - Verrett, Shirley, 1961 August 8; 27 photographic prints (Box 141, Folder 2637)
      - Walker, Margaret, 1942 November 27; 4 photographic prints (Box 141, Folder 2638)
      - Wallace, Emmett Babe, 1943 January 6; 15 photographic prints (Box 141, Folder 2639)
      - Warfield, William, 1951 February 7; 11 photographic prints (Box 141, Folder 2640)
      - Warfield, William, 1951 April 18; 5 photographic prints (Box 141, Folder 2641)
      - Washington, Fredi, 1933 March 18; 10 photographic prints (Box 141, Folder 2642)
      - Washington, Fredi, 1938 December 8; 8 photographic prints (Box 141, Folder 2643)
      - Waters, Ethel, 1932 June 8; 1 photographic print (Box 142, Folder 2644)
      - Waters, Ethel, 1932 June 8; 4 photographic prints (Box 142, Folder 2645)
      - Waters, Ethel, 1938 August 28; 12 photographic prints (Box 142, Folder 2646)
      - Waters, Ethel, 1938 August 28; 16 photographic prints (Box 142, Folder 2647)
      - Waters, Ethel, 1938 December 6; 8 photographic prints (Box 142, Folder 2648)
      - Waters, Ethel, 1939 February 19; 75 photographic prints Housed in 3 folders (Box 142, Folder 2649-2651)
      - Waters, Ethel, as Carmen in Carmen, opera by Georges Bizet and libretto by Henri Meilhac and Ludovic Halévy, 1934 April 30; 13 photographic prints (Box 142, Folder 2652)
      - Waters, Ethel, as Hagar in Mamba's Daughters, play by Dorothy Heyward and DuBose Heyward, 1939 February 19; 48 photographic prints (Box 142, Folder 2653-2654)
      - Waters, Ethel, as Hagar in Mamba's Daughters, play by Dorothy Heyward and DuBose Heyward, 1939 February 19; 100 photographic prints Housed in 4 folders (Box 143, Folder 2655-2658)
      - Waters, Ethel, as Petunia Jackson in Cabin in the Sky, musical with music by Vernon Duke, book by Lynn Root, lyrics by John La Touche, and vocal arrangements by Hugh Martin, 1940 November 17; 11 photographic prints (Box 143, Folder 2659)
      - Waters, Ethel, singing "Stormy Weather" by Harold Arlen and Ted Koehler, 1933 June 22; 43 photographic prints (Box 143, Folder 2660-2661)
      - Waters, Ethel, singing "Underneath the Harlem Moon" by Mack Gordon and Harry Revel, 1933 June 22; 29 photographic prints (Box 143, Folder 2662)
      - Waters, Ethel, with a sculpture, Ethel Waters, by Antonio Salemme, 1932 June 8; 1 photographic print (Box 143, Folder 2663)
      - Welch, Elisabeth, 1933 January 19; 26 photographic prints (Box 143, Folder 2664)
        Includes images of Welch with a sculpture, Ethel Waters, 1928, by Antonio Salemme.
      - Welch, Elisabeth, 1946 June 12; 7 photographic prints (Box 143, Folder 2665)
      - Wesley, Dorothy Porter, 1951 May 23; 3 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2666)
      - West, Dorothy, 1948 May 17; 5 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2667)
      - Weston, M. Moran, 1961 May 29; 6 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2668)
      - White, Carol Carr, and Josh White, 1946 August 13; 3 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2669)
      - White, Jane, 1941 September 16; 4 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2670)
      - White, Josh, 1946 August 13; 23 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2671)
      - White, Leah Gladys Powell, 1938 December 30; 6 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2672)
      - White, Portia, 1944 December 2; 17 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2673)
      - White, Walter, 1935 January 9; 2 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2674)
      - White, Walter, 1938 July 12; 4 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2675)
      - White, Walter Carl Darrow, 1938 December 30; 4 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2676)
      - White, Walter Carl Darrow, 1942 November 29; 4 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2677)
      - White, Walter, and Walter Carl Darrow White, 1942 November 29; 3 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2678)
      - Wilkins, Roy, 1958 May 27; 3 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2679)
      - Williams, Billy Dee, as The Boy in A Taste of Honey, play by Shelagh Delaney, 1963 January 29; 1 photographic print (Box 144, Folder 2680)
        Inscription on verso misidentifies him as a role in in Tiger, Tiger Burning Bright, play by Peter S. Feibleman.
      - Williams, Burton, 1961 April 4; 1 photographic print (Box 144, Folder 2681)
      - Williams, Camilla, 1946 May 31; 25 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2682)
      - Williams, John A., 1962 July 3; 54 photographic prints (Box 144, Folder 2683-2684)
      - Williams, Paul R., 1936 March 14; 8 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2685)
      - Williford, Maurice, 1963 August 28; 2 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2686)
      - Wilson, Ellis, 1948 April 15; 15 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2687)
      - Wilson, Ellis, 1959 August 12; 3 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2688)
      - Work, Frederick J. (Frederick Jerome), at the home of Albert C. (Albert Coombs) Barnes, Lower Merion Township, Pennsylvania, 1940 February 4; 7 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2689)
      - Work, John W. (John Wesley), at Fisk University, Nashville, Tennessee, 1947 April 26; 5 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2690)
      - Wright, Dale R., 1951 August 3; 2 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2691)
      - Wright, Ellen Poplar, and Richard Wright, 1945 October 27; 7 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2692)
      - Wright, Richard, 1939 June 23; 1 photographic print (Box 145, Folder 2693)
      - Wright, Richard, 1945 October 27; 5 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2694)
      - Wright, Richard, 1946 March 8; 8 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2695)
      - Wyckoff, William "Stumpy", in This Is the Army, musical with music by Irving Berlin and book by Irving Berlin and James McColl, 1942 August 11; 3 photographic prints (Box 145, Folder 2696)
    - Stage Door Canteen (American Theatre Wing)
      - Archer, Osceola, with Michael Bonifazio, Jimmie Daniels, Marcel Gonthier, Elaine Kent, Frank "Killer Joe" Piro, and Helene Tsang, 1943 June 21; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2697)
      - Ford, Helen, with Langston Hughes and Terry Keane, 1943 April 8; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2698)
      - LeNoire, Rosetta, 1942 September 11; 8 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2699)
    - Events
      Organized under six headings for New York City Parades; Josephine Baker Day, Harlem, New York City; Carl Van Vechten: His Gifts to Yale. An Exhibition in Honor of His Seventy-fifth Birthday at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut; Wedding of Carmen De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder at Christ & Holy Trinity Episcopal Church, Westport, Connecticut; Wedding Reception for Carmen De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder at the Clarence Derwent House, Westport, Connecticut; Party Hosted by Nora Douglas Holt for Singers, James Weldon Johnson Memorial Collection of Negro Arts and Letters at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut; and Performances.
      - New York City Parades
        - Brooklyn. Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks parade, 1936 August 25; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2700)
        - Brooklyn. Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks parade, 1936 August 25; 3 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2701)
        - Harlem. Improved Benevolent and Protective Order of the Elks parade, 1939 August 22; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2702)
      - Josephine Baker Day, Harlem, New York City
        - Baker, Josephine, in automobile, 1951 May 20; 4 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2703)
        - Hotel Theresa, crowd outside, 1951 May 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2704)
        - Hotel Theresa, Skyline Room, luncheon, 1951 May 20; 5 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2705)
        - Major, Gerri, 1951 May 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2706)
        - Morningside Park, crowd and speakers' stand, 1951 May 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2707)
        - Morningside Park, crowd and speakers' stand, 1951 May 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2708)
        - Park Palace Ballroom, cocktail dansante, 1951 May 20; 13 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2709)
        - Park Palace Ballroom, cocktail dansante. Major, Gerri, and Lindsay H. White, 1951 May 20; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2710)
      - Carl Van Vechten: His Gifts to Yale. An Exhibition in Honor of His Seventy-fifth Birthday at the Yale University Library, New Haven, Connecticut
        - Banks, Richard, and Nora Douglas Holt, 1955 June 22; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2711)
      - Wedding of Carmen De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder at Christ & Holy Trinity Episcopal Church, Westport, Connecticut
        - Mauriber, Saul, with Josephine Premice as well as a woman and man, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2712)
      - Wedding Reception for Carmen De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder at the Clarence Derwent House, Westport, Connecticut
        - Banfield, Clive, with Carmen De Lavallade, Elaine De Lavallade, and Geoffrey Holder, 1955 June 26; 3 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2713)
        - Camacho, Leu, with Elaine De Lavallade, Hubert Dilworth, Geoffrey Holder, and Lew Smith, 1955 June 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2714)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, 1955 June 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2715)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, with Elaine De Lavallade and Geoffrey Holder, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2716)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, with Elaine De Lavallade, Arthur Holder, and Louise de Frense Holder, 1955 June 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2717)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, with Geoffrey Holder, and Lucille Lortel, 1955 June 26; 3 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2718)
        - De Lavallade, Carmen, with Geoffrey Holder, Fania Marinoff, and Carl Van Vechten, 1955 June 26; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2719)
        - Wedding cake, 1955 June 26; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2720)
      - Performances
        - Davis, Sammy, Jr., at a National Urban League benefit at Birdland, Manhattan, New York City, 1956 June 10; 4 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2721)
        - Robeson, Paul, as Joe, during a performance of Showboat, musical with music by Jerome Kern and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, at the Casino Theatre, 1932 August 1; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2722)
    - Places
      - New York City. Harlem. West Indian Day Parade, 1949 September 3; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2723)
        Spectators on street from the apartment of Dorothy Randolph Peterson.
      - New York City. Manhattan. American Museum of Natural History. Equestrian Statue of Theodore Roosevelt, sculpture by James Earle Fraser, 1944 June 10; 3 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2724)
      - New York City. Manhattan. Central Park. USS Maine National Monument. Views of boys in the fountain, 1937 August 12; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2725)
      - New York City. Manhattan. Central Park. USS Maine National Monument. Views of boys in the fountain, 1937 September 3; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2726)
      - New York City. Manhattan. Empire Theatre. Cast list outside the theater for Mamba's Daughters, play by Dorothy Heyward and DuBose Heyward, 1938 December 26; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2727)
    - Artwork
      - Barthé, Richmond. Feral Benga, 1935, sculpture, 1937 July 11; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2728)
      - Barthé, Richmond. Head of Jimmie Daniels, circa 1933, sculpture, 1938 December 21; 4 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2729)
      - Barthé, Richmond. Julius, circa 1940, sculpture, 1940 October 23; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2730)
      - Bolling, Leslie Garland. The Boxer [Wild Cat], circa 1930, woodcarving, 1933 December 4; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2731)
        Roll number XXVI e.
      - Bolling, Leslie Garland. The Boxer [Wild Cat], circa 1930, woodcarving, 1933 October 20; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2732)
        Roll number X e.
      - Bolling, Leslie Garland. The Boxer [Wild Cat], circa 1930, woodcarving, 1937 April 6; 4 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2733)
        Roll number XX k.
      - Bolling, Leslie Garland. Woman's Head, circa 1930, woodcarving, 1935 April 14; 3 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2734)
      - Epstein, Jacob. Paul Robeson, 1928, sculpture, 1933 September 5; 14 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2735)
      - Epstein, Jacob. Paul Robeson, 1928, sculpture, 1935 April 14; 6 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2736)
      - Holder, Geoffrey. Voodoo Ceremony (Self-portrait), 1955, painting, 1955 June 17; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2737)
      - Salemme, Antonio. Ethel Waters, 1928, sculpture, 1932 February 22; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2738)
      - Savage, Augusta. James Weldon Johnson, 1938, sculpture, 1938 July 26; 6 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2739)
      - Savage, Augusta. The Harp ("Lift Every Voice and Sing"), 1939, sculpture, 1939 May 8; 1 photographic print (Box 146, Folder 2740)
        Roll number XXII o. Print from the Langston Hughes bequest.
      - Wilson, Ellis, Marchand, circa 1947, painting, 1959 August 12; 2 photographic prints (Box 146, Folder 2741)
  - Photographic Postcards, 12 linear feet